Guide to the Labor Union Constitutions, By-Laws and Agreements collection, 1883-1999 LAC0012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Agreements, 1910-1999; Series 2; 7 Linear Feet
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Experess and Station Employees, 1975 June 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1958 July 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1958 July 16; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1953 January 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Pullman Company.
  - Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, 1954 March 22; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Agreement with the Narragansett Electric Company.
  - Campbell Soup Company, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Airways Inc., 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Airways Inc. And The Flight Attendants, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Airways, Inc. And The Flight Engineers, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Central States Area Local Cartage Agreement, 1955-1961; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Central States Area-Over-the-road Motor Freigh Agreement, 1958-1964; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - The Clerical Employes' Association, 1930 May 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the Oregon Short Line Railroad Company.
  - City Products Corp. Merchants Ice and Coal Co., 1956; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Colonial Stores Inc., 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Communication Workers of America, 1971 July 18; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Agreement with Southwestern Bell.
  - Conductors, Trainmen and Yardmen of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1926 December 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company.
  - Contract Information, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Construction Industry, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Engineers, Firemen and Hostlers of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1922 November 24; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Engineers, Firemen and Hostlers of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1924 April 11; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company
  - Fifteen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1944 January 17; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fifteen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1954 August 21; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Five Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1964 November 20; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Five Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1965 February 17; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fourteen Participating Labor Organizations, 1941 December 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fourteen Participating Labor Organizations, 1941 December 17; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Gamble - Skogmo, Inc., 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Launderers, 1970-1975; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - International Airlines Pilot Association, 1988-2003; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Machinists, 1954 July 19; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Agreement with the Boeing Airplane Company.
  - International Association of Machinists, 1962 March 1; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Agreement with Philips Electronic Instruments.
  - International Association of Machinists, 1965 November 8; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Agreement with the McDonnell Aircraft Corporation.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1946; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Agreement with the National Electrical Contractors Association
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1953 May 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Agreement with the Connecticut Power Company.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1953 June 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Connecticut Light and Power Company.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1954 October 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Agreement with General Insulated Wire Works, Inc.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1957 April 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1920 January 16; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers, Helpers, Roundhouse and Railway Shop Laborers, 1942 August 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad Company.
  - International Longshoremen's Association, 1954 October 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Agreement with the New York Shipping Association.
  - International Molders and Foundry Workers Union of North America, 1948 January 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the Manufacturers' Protective and Development Association.
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1956 October 17; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Underwood Corporation.
  - International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal and Soft Drink Workers of America, 1939 November 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Agreement with Brewers and Ice Manufacturers of St. Louis, Missouri and Vicinity.
  - Inside Workers in Manufacturing, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Joint Council No. 7, 1985-1988; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Joint Council Dining Car Employes' of the Hotel and Restaurant Employe's International Alliance and Bartenders' International League of America, 1945 September 10; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Kroehler MFG. Co. Rider, 31 March 1970; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Kroehler MFG. Co. Rider, 30 June 1973; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Lansing Schools Education Association Master Agreement with Lansing School District, 1976-1979; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lime Stone and Quarry Companies, 1956; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Linen Rental Employers, 1969-1976; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Local 480-Penn Truck Aids, Inc., 1979-1982; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Local 682, 1957-1959; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Locomotive Engineers of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1955 March 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Locomotive Firemen of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1910 June 11; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Locomotive Firemen of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1913 May 13; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Master Freight Info, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Master Cement, 1970-1973; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Master Cement, 1973-1982; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Master Cement, 1982-1985; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Master Cement, 1994-1998; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Mechanical Department Association of the Burlington Railroad, 1926 November 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1968; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Misc. and Various Contracts Including UPS, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Missouri - Kansas - Texas Association of Shop-Employes, 1929 March 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Agreement with the Missouri - Kansas - Texas Railroad Company.
  - National Air Freight Forwarding Industry, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - National Grievance Comm and Misc. Info, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - National Master Freight Agreement, 1970 April 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - National Master Freight Agreement, February 1964-March 1967; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - National Master Freight Agreement, April 1994-March 1998; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern conference Area, March 1982-March 1985; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1985-March 1988; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1985-March 1988; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, 1988-1991; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Western Conference Area, 1988-1991; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1988-March 1991; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1988-March 1991; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1988-March 1991; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1991-March 1994; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1994-March 1998; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, 1998-2003; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1967-March 1970; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1970-June 1973; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1970-June 1973; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, July 1973-March 1976; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1976-March 1979; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement-Southern Conference Area, April 1979-March 1982; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - National Master United Parcel Service Agreement, 1979-1982; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - National Wire Weavers Agreement, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - New Jersey Brewers' Association, 1964-1967; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - New York Stereotypers' Union No. 1, 1963 March 31; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Agreement with the Publishers' Association of New York City.
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, 1956 November 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Agreement with the New York Times Company.
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, 2009-2014; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1939 May 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    Agreement with the Texas and Pacific Railway Company.
  - The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1939 November 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1951 February 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1959 October 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1962 November 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1941 May 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Agreement with the Union Railroad Company.
  - Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1945 September 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1947 November 14; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1951 January 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Order of Railway Conductors of America, 1954 February 5; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen and the Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1957 November 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1957 November 16; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1961 January 18; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - PanAm Teamsters, 1 January 1978; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Tea Company, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Railway Express, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Railway Employees Department of the AFL, 1919; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Railway Employes' Department of the AFL, 1921 July 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the Chicago and North Western Railway Company.
  - Railway Employees Department of the AFL, 1946 July 16; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Agreement with the New York Central Railroad, Michigan Central Railroad, and Boston and Albany Railroad.
  - Railway Employes' Department of the AFL, 1952 April 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Agreement with the Pennsylvania Railroad Company.
  - Railway Patrolmen's Unions, 1949 September 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1954 August 12; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1958 June 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1965 January 29; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Agreement with Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees.
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1963 April 25; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Agreement with the F.B. Rogers Silver Company.
  - Rhode Island State Employees Association, 1975 December 1; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Agreement with the State of Rhode Island.
  - Saturn Airways, Inc. And Aaxico Airlines, Inc., 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Screen Actors Guild Codified Basic Agreement for Independent Producers, 1989; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Seventeen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1947 July 25; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Seventeen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1947 September 3; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Seventeen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1947 September 7; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Shopmen's Association, 1933 December 1; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Site Improvement Association, 1974-1977; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Sixteen Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1949 March 19; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Southwest Airlines Co., 16 February 2009; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Southern Conference-Over-the-road Motor Freight Agreement, 1961-1964; Series 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Springmeier Shipping, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937 March 17; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation.
  - St. Louis and St. Louis County Hardwood and Softwood Lumber Yards, 1955-1984; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis Material Dealers Association, 1957-1984; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - St. louis Material Dealers Association, n.d.; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America, 1954 April 22; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Agreement with the Western Carriers' Conference Committee.
  - Teamster Airline Division Agreements, Summary, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Textile Workers Union of America, 1953 April 16; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company, Inc.
  - Textile Workers Union of America, 1956 April 15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Agreement with the American Thread Company.
  - Textile Workers Union of America, 1966 April 16; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Agreement with Berkshire Hathaway, Inc.
  - Transportation Corporation of America, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Transportation Corporation of America, 1964; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Trustees Of The Property Of New York, New Haven And Hartford Railroad, Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - UAW - Local 306 Collective Bargaining with The Budd Company, 1988-1992; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - UFCW - Local 400 Collective Bargaining Agreement, 2001; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Agreement with General Motors Corporation, 1993 October 24; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America, 1949 November 16; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Agreement with Vermont Furniture Company, Inc.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1953 May 18; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the Whitney Chain Company.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1953 October 13; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Marlin-Rockwell Corporation.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1954 March 1; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Agreement with Chase Brass and Copper Company, Inc.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1954 October 15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Agreement with the Seymour Manufacturing Company.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1954 November 10; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Agreement with Colt's Manufacturing Company.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1954 November 27; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the Anemostat Corporation of America.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1955 September 1; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Agreement with the Chrysler Corporation.
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1958 November 16; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1962 November 2; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1979 September 14; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    Agreement with the General Motors Corporation.
  - United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, 1955 February 16; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Agreement with the Ruberoid Company.
  - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1955 May 15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Agreement with the Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company.
  - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1955 May 15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Agreement with the PIttsburgh Plate Glass Company.
  - United Railroad Workers of America, 1949 July 1; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - United Rubber Workers of America, 1941 November 19; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Agreement with the Armstrong Rubber Company.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1950 April 5; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Agreement with the United States Rubber Company.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1953 September 15; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Agreement with the Bristol Manufacturing Corporation.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastics Workers of America, 1954 August 1; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Agreement with the Hodgman Rubber Company.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 April 8; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 May 17; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 May 22; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the Armstrong-Norwalk Rubber Corporation.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 July 15; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1955 October 30; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the Seamless Rubber Company.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1957 April 9; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1957 August 8; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1958 October 30; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Carr Manufacturing Corporation, Carr Fulflex, Inc.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1960 September 9; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1963 September 9; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1966 August 1; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Agreement with Carr-Fulflex, Inc.
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America New Amendments to Constitution, 1970 November; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1949 March 6; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the Whiting and Davis Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1950 November 1; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Agreement with the Newman-Crosby Steel Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1952 July 22; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Agreement with the Grinnell Corporation, Auburn Plant.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1952 July 22; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Agreement with the Grinnell Corporation, Providence Plant.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1952 August 28; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Agreement with the Wyckoff Steel Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1952 October 6; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Agreement with the National Plainfield Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 April 1; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Agreement with the American Screw Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 June 21; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Agreement with Jenkins Bros.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 July 1; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Agreement with Farrel-Birmingham Company, Inc.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 July 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Agreement with the Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 August 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Agreement with the Aluminum Company of America.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1954 October 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1955 June 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Hemphill Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 January 17; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Agreement with B-I-F Industries, Inc.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 February 13; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the Grinnell Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America Agreement with the American Screw Company, 2 copies, May 1956; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 May 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 August 3; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the United States Steel Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 August 4; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1956 August 6; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1958 February 7; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Agreementw with B-I-F Industries, Inc.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1958 March 19; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Agreement with the Standard Die Set Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1959 May 13; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Agreement with the William H. Haskell Manufacturing Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1959 October 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1959 October 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Agreement wtih Whitin Machine Works.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1960 January 4; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1960 March 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Agreement with Crescent Company, Inc.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1961 March 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1961 November 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Agreement with the Thomson-National Press Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 February 7; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 April 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    Agreement with North American Philips Co., Inc.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 April 1; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Agreement with Whitin Machine Works.